{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist of the anime series Naruto?",
        "answers": [
          "Naruto Uzumaki",
          "Sasuke Uchiha",
          "Sakura Haruno"
        ],
        "correct": "Naruto Uzumaki"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in Attack on Titan?",
        "answers": [
          "Eren Yeager",
          "Levi Ackerman",
          "Mikasa Ackerman"
        ],
        "correct": "Eren Yeager"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the magical world where the anime Little Witch Academia is set?",
        "answers": [
          "Luna Nova",
          "Hogwarts",
          "Mahoutokoro"
        ],
        "correct": "Luna Nova"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the demon who possesses the protagonist in the anime series Demon Slayer?",
        "answers": [
          "Tanjiro Kamado",
          "Nezuko Kamado",
          "Muzan Kibutsuji"
        ],
        "correct": "Muzan Kibutsuji"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in the anime series One Piece?",
        "answers": [
          "Monkey D. Luffy",
          "Roronoa Zoro",
          "Nami"
        ],
        "correct": "Monkey D. Luffy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in Death Note?",
        "answers": [
          "Light Yagami",
          "L Lawliet",
          "Misa Amane"
        ],
        "correct": "Light Yagami"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in Fullmetal Alchemist?",
        "answers": [
          "Edward Elric",
          "Alphonse Elric",
          "Roy Mustang"
        ],
        "correct": "Edward Elric"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in Cowboy Bebop?",
        "answers": [
          "Spike Spiegel",
          "Jet Black",
          "Faye Valentine"
        ],
        "correct": "Spike Spiegel"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the magical item that gives Usagi Tsukino her powers in Sailor Moon?",
        "answers": [
          "Moon Crystal",
          "Star Seed",
          "Sailor Crystal"
        ],
        "correct": "Moon Crystal"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in the anime series Sword Art Online?",
        "answers": [
          "Kirito",
          "Asuna",
          "Sinon"
        ],
        "correct": "Kirito"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the pirate crew led by Monkey D. Luffy in One Piece?",
        "answers": [
          "Straw Hat Pirates",
          "Blackbeard Pirates",
          "Whitebeard Pirates"
        ],
        "correct": "Straw Hat Pirates"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the high school attended by the main characters in the anime series K-On!?",
        "answers": [
          "Sakuragaoka High School",
          "Hokago Tea Time High School",
          "Mio and Ritsu's High School"
        ],
        "correct": "Sakuragaoka High School"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in the anime series My Hero Academia?",
        "answers": [
          "Izuku Midoriya",
          "Katsuki Bakugo",
          "Shoto Todoroki"
        ],
        "correct": "Izuku Midoriya"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the organization that employs the main character in the anime series Psycho-Pass?",
        "answers": [
          "Public Safety Bureau",
          "Criminal Investigation Division",
          "Judiciary Police"
        ],
        "correct": "Public Safety Bureau"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the giant humanoid creatures that the characters in Attack on Titan fight against?",
        "answers": [
          "Titans",
          "Giants",
          "Colossi"
        ],
        "correct": "Titans"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in the anime series Dragon Ball Z?",
        "answers": [
            "Goku",
            "Vegeta",
            "Gohan"
        ],
        "correct": "Goku"
        },
        {
        "question": "What is the name of the magical girl in the anime series Cardcaptor Sakura?",
        "answers": [
            "Sakura Kinomoto",
            "Tomoyo Daidouji",
            "Meiling Li"
        ],
        "correct": "Sakura Kinomoto"
        },
        {
        "question": "What is the name of the protagonist in the anime series One-Punch Man?",
        "answers": [
            "Saitama",
            "Genos",
            "Mumen Rider"
        ],
        "correct": "Saitama"
        },
        {
        "question": "What is the name of the school attended by the main characters in the anime series Assassination Classroom?",
        "answers": [
            "Kunugigaoka Junior High School",
            "Yokai Academy",
            "Otonokizaka High School"
        ],
        "correct": "Kunugigaoka Junior High School"
        },
        {
        "question": "What is the name of the powerful sword wielded by the main character in the anime series Bleach?",
        "answers": [
            "Zangetsu",
            "Tensa Zangetsu",
            "Bankai"
        ],
        "correct": "Zangetsu"
        },
        {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in the anime series Black Clover?",
        "answers": [
            "Asta",
            "Yuno",
            "Noelle Silva"
        ],
        "correct": "Asta"
        },
        {
        "question": "What is the name of the organization that employs the main characters in the anime series Ghost in the Shell?",
        "answers": [
            "Public Security Section 9",
            "Section 6",
            "Ministry of Internal Affairs"
        ],
        "correct": "Public Security Section 9"
        },
        {
        "question": "What is the name of the magical girl group in the anime series Puella Magi Madoka Magica?",
        "answers": [
            "Magical Girls of Mitakihara",
            "Magical Five",
            "Puella Magi"
        ],
        "correct": "Puella Magi"       
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the high school attended by the main characters in the anime series My Hero Academia?",
        "answers": [
          "UA High School",
          "Yuei High School",
          "Shiketsu High School"
        ],
        "correct": "UA High School"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in the anime series Hunter x Hunter?",
        "answers": [
          "Gon Freecss",
          "Killua Zoldyck",
          "Hisoka Morow"
        ],
        "correct": "Gon Freecss"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in the anime series JoJo's Bizarre Adventure?",
        "answers": [
          "Jotaro Kujo",
          "Joseph Joestar",
          "Jonathan Joestar"
        ],
        "correct": "Jonathan Joestar"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the organization that employs the main characters in the anime series Attack on Titan?",
        "answers": [
          "Survey Corps",
          "Military Police Brigade",
          "Garrison Regiment"
        ],
        "correct": "Survey Corps"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the organization that employs the main characters in the anime series Naruto?",
        "answers": [
          "Konohagakure",
          "Akatsuki",
          "Orochimaru"
        ],
        "correct": "Konohagakure"
      }
    ]
}
    